Hello friends, my name is Vikram and
welcome again to our YouTube channel
Technical friends, I have brought you information that due to
people's interest in Dari IS A Separate and Social Life Insurance, there was no interest here
but now the recruitment has
started again in which all the experienced and
experienced candidates can apply,
if you come and look at their website, then
you will see a lot of recruitment in which
applications are sought for the post of Senior Para Active Service Manager and Financial Service, this recruitment is for the post of Penal Service Manager and Civil Service Consultant,
different locations are repeated, it is good
that you apply for your location,
Bihar, West Bengal, Gujarat, Kerala,
apart from that, if you come up, then there are
many recruitments here too which are in
different places for which you can apply, the
good things about all these recruitments are that
from acupressure to experienced
candidates can now afford it, or
friends, by applying for one you can
Buddha, see for yourself the rest below.
Before that, there are a couple of things that I'll clarify first:
when you apply for this,
you don't need to pay any fees.
If you want to apply,
go to their official website and apply.
Don't use any third-party tool because that does
n't achieve anything. Your data goes to them.
After that, they call you from different sources,
demanding money. You do
n't need to pay any fees.
You can use this method by going to their website. You can send the
message I'm about to share
and submit your application.
If they like your profile,
you'll be
notified via email. If you do
n't like it,
they won't provide you with any information. So
now let's talk about the Relativity Light
Area and how to apply. So
friends, let's do it for one. So
first, let's do it. This
is a recruitment for Abe Sibal in Kolkata.  Of
recruitment
natural service uncertainty rest you can see that
in Amazing no kind of experience
is considered otherwise if you
want to apply then you can do it or friends
as you open it then almost the
description here is almost the theme or it is
clearly written that you have graduation or
post graduation that you can apply in this system there is
no test of any kind
we have not asked for any special thing that only if
you have done graduation
you can apply in any stream
similarly if you look at the rest of the stream
like suppose this is
in cricket you will click here by clicking on
biscuit many things are
written here graduates are post graduates
can apply graduate fresh air
or you have some kind of experience
from these things up to 5 years see if you
have experience of time also then
you can like it now so
friends this is the way to see the description
now let's talk about the selection process  The
selection will be based on your interview.
If your profile is
liked, you will be informed through the mail
and the online interview will be for the
selection of the beginning of the Sufi Festival. Talking about the
salary, nothing has been said about the salary here. It is
possible that your
salary may be a little better. It
depends on the location. If your city
is a metro city or a big city, then you will
get a little more salary, but if you
go on your smartphone, then the salary there is a
little less. But here the salary has
not been said about it. Now friends, let's talk about
how to apply. To apply,
create a button above. If you click on it,
you will see a button of lines
forming above. If you click on it, then
here you can see the number open inch.
This is five for Kochi. Experience from zero to 5
years, but still you can like.
Here you have to click on the browser and
upload your view,
but keep this thing in mind that the
size of your document or PDF should not be more than 3MB.
If you keep the format in one then only
you will be supported. First name, last name,
email account,
this number, click here and
click on submit application here.
As soon as you click, you just have to do this small
process and your application gets
submitted in their server, after that
they go to your job application,
if they feel that you are
eligible for the job then they will definitely
give you that information through email that when you have to
come for the interview, when you have to appear and
you have to give the interview online, so
friends this is the way to apply, if you are a
pimple then you can apply for these,
thank you very much for watching this video
and I hope that you
liked the video because if
you still have some questions related to the video then
you can write in the comment section,
subscribe to the channel, you get it from no
one, who is with you, till then take care of yourself